And all of that leads us into our final exercise.
So for intermediate Python, go to chapter 8, the final exercise.
We're going to build that basic web app that we saw earlier.
And let me kill the swine and bring up the window where I had it running.
So this basic web app, sorry.
Alas is to select our languages via checkbox and hit submit.
And with each submission, we don't have a database.
We're just hitting the GitHub API.
So for the few of you folks in class, as you build this,
if you kind of really mash all the buttons, you might hit the rate limit.
So just something to be mindful of.
And I can go and hit this API filter by whichever language I want.
Okay.
For this exercise, if you go to the class website,
you should have flask and requests installed already.
If you don't, you can take a look at this requirements.txt file that I put in with my with my package.
And this file is in the course repository.
So if you get poll, you'll get all the latest changes.
This lists all of the libraries that are required to run my program.
You can even peg these to a specific version with the double equal signs if you want to.
You know, just an example there.
So if you didn't have the required dependencies installed,
you can do a Python dash and pip install.
And then pass the dash our flag to specify a file.
Once you advance in your Python journey and your requirements become more complicated,
you can use the more advanced pip end tool to handle complicated dependencies.
So just an important thing about this final exercise.
Download the zip file that contains the static files for this application.
And just like the templates directory where flask just knew all my templates lived in there.
For our static files, we have a static directory and flask just knows that those are our static files.
So I'm going to provide you with a CSS file and a index dot HTML template that does the ginger templating for you.
And you're going to write your own flask routing that takes.
The route is going to be at the root URL.
Our that route is going to accept a get and a post right when we submit a form that's going to be an HTTP post.
When we first visit the page that's just again.
And you're going to build that along with your with the static files that I provide.
You're also going to use some of the things that we learned earlier.
So the our GitHub repositories, those are going to be stored in our own class.
We're going to throw a custom exception.
Thanks for watching.